（神崎）う～わ！お…。
（男鹿）地獄投げ～！飛んでけ～。
うわ。
Hell Throw!
Take a flying leap!
（アランドロン）＜これは　ひょんな事から
赤ん坊を→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
育てる事になった
不良高校生の物語。ただし→
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
その赤ん坊は普通の
赤ん坊ではなく→
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
魔王の子だったのです＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
Is There a Special Move?
Ishiyama Park
（アランドロン）＜昔々　あるところに
それはそれは凶悪で→
Once upon a time, in a land far far away,
there was a barbaric, ruthless, and defiant,
残忍で傍若無人で
人を人とも思わぬ→
demon-like bastard who thought
nothing of his fellow man.
悪魔のような男がおりました。→
その男の名は…＞
And that man's name was...
男鹿～！
Oga!
ハァハァ…。
（城山）神崎さん！差し入れです。
Kanzaki-san! I brought you supplies.
…うむ。
で…調子は　どうですか？
So? How is it going?
ふ…浮かんだぜ　新・必殺技！
I've come up with my new special move!
そ　それは…。
T-That's...
今までの踵落としの２倍の威力。
Twice the power of my old heel drop...
に　２倍？
T-Twice?!
ダブル踵落とし！
うお…。
Double Heel Smash!
うわ～！…あ。
神崎…さん？
（神崎）…く。
Kanzaki...-san?
…な。
両足で踵落としをやれば→
I thought I could double the
power by dropping both heels,
威力は２倍と思ったが…どう
やりゃいいんだ？
But, how do I do it?
あの…。
（夏目）どう　頑張ってる？
Uh...
So, working hard?
夏目？
何しに来たんだ　最近→
Natsume! What are you here for?
I thought you were hanging
around Oga lately...
男鹿の周りを
チョロチョロしてると思ったが。
（夏目）
まあまあ　色々とさ
お役立ち情報を持って来たから。
Now, now... I've been collecting
some useful information.
男鹿ちゃんの戦いぶり　こっそり
撮影させてもらってたんだよね。
I secretly filmed how Oga-chan fights.
（夏目）さすがだね～男鹿ちゃん。
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]（ベル坊）ダ！
Just look at Oga-chan go...
ん…。こ　これは？
T-That's...!
わかりましたよ　神崎さん。男鹿の
強さの秘密が！
I've figured it out, Kanzaki-san!
I've figured out the
secret to Oga's strength!
なに？
What?!
どうです？赤ん坊を
常に背負う事によって→
What do you think? You'll
carry a baby on your back,
バランス感覚を磨き。そして
重いものを身に付ける事で→
which will help polish your balance,
and by adding weight, you'll train
your body to be more powerful!
筋力も鍛え上げる
パワーリスト効果。それが→
That's the secret to Oga's strength!
男鹿の強さの秘密です。
いや　しかし　こりゃ～。
Sure... But this...
（城山）なに言ってるんです。男鹿に
勝ちたくないんですか？
What are you saying? Don't
you want to beat Oga?
く…。
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]ダ！
わ　わかった。
これで完璧です。
F-Fine...
This will be perfect.
男鹿も同じように
常に赤ん坊を背負ったまま→
I'm sure Oga's raising a baby just like this,
日々　厳しい特訓をしているはず。
and undergoing harsh training every day!
ふわ～。
ダ～ブ　ダ～ブ。ダダダ…。
ダブ～！
（ヒルダ）坊っちゃまは→
The master is saying he wishes
to go outside somewhere.
お出かけしたがっておられるぞ。
ん？めんどくせえから→
What a pain. Maybe some other time.
また後でな。
ダ～。
ハァハァ…。
≪何あれ≫
≪怖いよ～ママ≫
What is that?
I'm scared, Mom!
≪警察呼んだ方が良くない？≫
Shouldn't we call the police?
なあ　城山
妙に見られてる気がするんだが…。
Hey. Shiroyama... Don't you get the
feeling... people are looking at us funny?
いえ気のせいです。
そ　そうか。
No, it's your imagination.
I-Is it?
それより神崎さん。
どうした？
Anyway, Kanzaki-san...
What is it?
首が落ちてます。
（神崎）あ…。
The head fell off.
（夏目）お～い神崎くん。
Hey, Kanzaki-kun!
それだけじゃ　パワーリスト効果は
生まれないと思ってさ→
I don't think doing only that will
give you a power wrist effect.
ダンベルとか買って来たよ。
I bought dumbbells.
あ？
なるほど。
I see!
どう？
へ　軽いもんだぜ。
This ain't nothing.
ハ　ハハハ…軽い　軽い。→
Nothing! Nothing at all!
ハハ　ハハハ…。
それじゃ　もうちょい。
Then... a little more.
ん。まだまだ　もっと入れろ。→
More! Put in more!
ん。ハ　ハ　ハ…。
も　もっと。
（城山）神崎さん　こんなモノが…。
More...
Kanzaki-san, look what I found!
もっと！
（城山）神崎さ～ん。
There's more?!
Kanzaki-san!
（夏目）あれ？
Oh?
（神崎）く…。
神崎さん。今のは→
Kanzaki-san...
The problem was that we were using a fake.
まがい物だったから
ダメだったんですよ。
どういう事だ？
つまり本物の赤ん坊なら。
What do you mean?
Basically, if it were a real baby, instead...
なるほどね。けど　その本物の
赤ん坊は　どっから連れて来るの？
I see.
But where are you going
to get this "real" baby?
う。そ　それは。
W-Well...
へ…。それくらいなら　俺に任せろ。
Just leave that much to me.
（神崎の父）≪どうしたんだ？急に
改まって話などと≫
What's this thing you wanted
to talk with me about?
（神崎）≪頼みがある　オヤジ≫
（神崎の父）≪頼み？≫
I have a favor to ask, Pops!
A favor?
（神崎）≪今すぐに
俺の弟を作ってくれ！≫
Make me a little brother, right now!
Kanzaki
（殴られる音）
うお～！
神崎さん。
神崎くんのオヤジさん
とても怖いんだね。
Kanzaki-san!
Kanzaki-kun's old man is
quite scary, isn't he?
オヤジの野郎
我が子の頼みぐらい…う。
Damn you, Pops!
Not even listening to the
requests of his own kid!
もしかしたら　赤ん坊に
こだわらなくても→
Maybe it doesn't really
matter if it's a baby...
良いのかもしれません。
どういう事だ？
What do you mean?
そう　例えば…む？
Right... For instance...
ニャ～。
ニャ～！
待て　待つんだネコ。
神崎さんの為に。
Wait! Wait there, cat!
This is for Kanzaki-san's training!
う～。
ニャ～。
よしよし…。
ネコはダメだ。
How'd the cat idea go?
No use!
す　すいませんでした！ここは
やはり人間で…む。
I-I'm sorry!
It definitely needs to be a human!
…そう言えばさ
ほのかん家の変なオッサン→
So, about that weird big guy
at your house, Honoka...
あれ何なの？
ドロンドロンだっけ？
Who is he?
That guy named Dron-dron or something?
（ほのか）私も　よく
わからないんだけど→
I don't really know myself. My brother
just brought him home one day.
お兄ちゃんが勝手に
連れて来ちゃって。
君たち！
（３人）へ？
You three!
頼む！神崎さんの為に
おんぶさせてくれないか～！
Please! For Kanzaki-san's
sake, will you ride on him?!
（パトカーのサイレン）
（夏目）うんうん
あれは仕方ないよね～。
Yeah, can't get around that...
ん～。
人形もダメ　本物の赤ん坊もダメ→
A doll isn't going to work.
Neither is a real baby.
ネコも女子中学生もダメ。
あとは残るは…。
Cats and middle school girls are also nixed.
All that's left is...
（城山）神崎さん。
ん？
Kanzaki-san...
…城山　どこ行ってたんだ？
あ　あの。
Shiroyama.
Where did you go?
U-Um...
あん？
神崎さんの為に　この俺を
役立てて下ちゃい。
Please, make use of me, Kanzaki-san!
…お　お前。
You are...
赤ん坊にしては　でかくて重いのは
百も承知。しかし→
I know that I'm far bigger
and heavier than a baby.
But even so, I want to be of
assistance to you, Kanzaki-san!
どうしても神崎さんの
お役に立ちたいんです。
いや　そう言われても。
（城山）神崎さん。
Yeah... I see your point, but...
Kanzaki-san!
あ？
（城山）男鹿に
勝ちたくないんですか？
Don't you want to beat Oga?
…く。
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]ダ～ブ！
わ　わかった。
神崎さん。
A-All right...
Kanzaki-san...
待った！
ん？
Wait.
それじゃあ　ダメなんじゃ
ないかな～。大きさや重さ以外に→
That's not going to work.
It's not just your size and
weight that's different.
男鹿ちゃんの背負ってる赤ん坊と
決定的な違いがあるし。
There's also a crucial
difference with Oga's baby.
決定的な…。
違い？
Crucial...
...difference?
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]ダブ？
も　もちかして。
そう。男鹿ちゃんの背負っている→
Could you mean...
Yes! The baby on Oga-chan's
back is always naked!
赤ん坊は常にハダカ！
ハダカ　ハダカ。
Naked!
ハダカ　ハダカ　ハダカ！
Naked?
Naked...
Naked!
やめとけ　城山。
何も　そこまで…。
Don't do it, Shiroyama!
You really don't have to go that far...
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]ダブ？
いえ　やります！
No, I'll do it!
神崎さんの為ならば！…どうです。
（悲鳴）
If it's for you, Kanzaki-san, I'll...
How about this?
お　おう。
（城山）それじゃ　早速→
U-Uh...
Now hurry up and put me on your back!
俺を背負って下さい。
（パトカーのサイレン）
大変だったね～。さて　次は
何してみよっか？
This sure is tricky.
Anyway, what should we try next?
もういい。
神崎さん。
Enough.
Kanzaki-san!
１人にしといてくれ。
Leave me alone.
（夏目）
あ～あ　神崎くん
すっかり元気なくしちゃって。
Kanzaki-kun's all down in the dumps.
夏目！元はと言えば
お前が悪いんだ。
Natsume! This is all your fault!
アハハハ。痛い　痛いな～。
Ow! That hurts!
…くそ！やはり俺は
ヤツに勝てないのか。
Shit! Is it impossible for me to beat him?
男鹿～！
Oga!
ん？
さっきから坊っちゃまが→
I told you. The master is bored.
退屈されていると言っておろう。
ダ…ダ～ブ！ダ～！
夕食まで時間がある
坊っちゃまを連れて→
There is time before dinner.
Take the master and go play somewhere.
早く遊びに行くが良い。
ダ～ダ。
日曜くらい　ゆっくりさせろよ。
う…ダ。イ～。
Can't I at least relax on Sundays?
ほら　今にも坊っちゃまが
泣き出しそうだぞ。
Look now... The master is about to cry...
あ～わかった。わかったよ。
ダ～！
Fine, I'll do it!
Take you to play somewhere, huh?
どこか遊びにったってなぁ～。
ゲーセンて訳にもいかねえし→
Guess an arcade isn't gonna work.
またあそこの公園かぁ？
ダダ　ダダ…！
Maybe that park again?
（古市）
おう　男鹿！どこ行くんだ？
Hey, Oga.
Where are you going?
へぇ～　公園にベル坊をねぇ。
Taking baby Beel to the park?
I wish Hilda-san would come.
ヒルダさんも来ればいいのにな。
いや　常連のママさん連中と→
Naw... It'd be a pain if she got
in a fight with the other moms.
揉め事でも起こされたら
めんどくせえし。
Other moms?
ママさん連中！？
ああ。
Yeah...
Are they young?
それって　若いのか！？
じゃね～か？→
I guess so. They're at least
younger than your mom.
少なくとも　お前のお袋よりはな。
((ボク　いくつなの？))
((うふっ　うちの子よりカワイイ))
How old are you?
You're cuter than my son!
Why don't we play together in the sandbox?
((一緒に　お砂場で遊ばない？))
エヘ　エヘヘヘ…。
よ～し　行こう！
公園だな　公園！→
Okay, let's go to the park!
Leave everything to me!
まかせとけ～！アハハハ…！
はあ？
ダァ？
Ishiyama Park
（邦枝）≪光太～？≫
Kota!
（邦枝）
光太～？どこなの～？
Kota! Where did you go?
ハァ～　どうしよう。
おっ！？
What'll I do?
ハッ！
よう　最近よく会うな。
Hey! We sure meet up a lot.
今日も子守りか？
あっ　それが…。
おおお～っ！
With the kid again today?
Actually...
（邦枝）《こいつ　いつも
男鹿にくっついてる…》
That's the guy who's always sticking to Oga!
あ　あなたは！
Y-You're...
Crap! He's probably figured
out my disguise, unlike Oga!
《やばっ！さすがに男鹿と
違って変装してるのバレた！？》
I can't believe this!
信じられない！
《そりゃ
信じられないでしょうよ。→
Well, sure it's unbelievable.
Me dressing so plainly and taking
a kid to play in the park...
こんな地味なカッコして　公園で
子供を遊ばせてるだなんて！》
何て…→
What a...
何て　若々しくて可愛らしい
奥様なんだぁぁ～！
What a super-cute and young mother!
はぁ？
（古市）いや～　高校生と言っても
十分通用しますよ～！
Huh?
If someone said you were in high
school I wouldn't bat an eye!
とても　お子さんが
いらっしゃるとは思えない！
I would never think you had a kid!
いや　そうじゃなくて…。
Um, that's not it...
Yes! That's not it!
そう！そうじゃなくて！
うん？
光太がいなくなっちゃったの！
Kota's missing!
（ガサッ）
うん？
（光太）ア～ア。
お前　どこのガキだ？
Where're you from, kid?
ア～ウ～ウ～。
うん？ブランコ乗りたいのか？
You wanna get on the swing?
アイ…ウ～！ウア～。
Hey, you okay?
おい　大丈夫か？
ア～ウ～！
あ？俺に漕げってか？
What, you want me to swing you?
ウ～　アウアウ…。
フッ…仕方ねえな。
I suppose...
アイ～！
So, having fun?
そうか　楽しいか。
アイ～！
Sheesh... I don't have time
to be playing with this kid.
まったく　こんなガキと
遊んでる場合じゃ…ん？
ア～。
んん？
ア～ア～ア～！
んんんん～！
（神崎）
≪ホントよね～≫
Seriously.
≪ああ　そうそう
昨日テレビでね～…≫
あ？
Oh yeah... Did you see it on TV yesterday?
あれって！？
前に来てた乱暴男よ！
イヤ～！
That's...
That's the violent man from before!
で　お子さんを見失ったのは
この辺りなんですね！？
You lost sight of him around here?
Yes. I took my eyes off
of him for a second...
ええ　ちょっと目を離した隙に…。
Oh, that's right!
そうだ　そう言えば
さっき　うちの妹が→
My little sister said there was
a suspicious person around here!
この近くで怪しいヤツに
会ったとか！
O-Oh no!
そ　そんな…。
どうせ　その辺で遊んでんだろ。
He's probably just playing
around here somewhere.
《男鹿！？私を安心させる
ために　そんな事を…→
Oga... Are you saying that to calm me down?
やっぱりコイツ
見かけによらず優しい》
He's so much kinder than he looks.
うちも怪しいヤツだろうが
強盗だろうが→
I wish someone suspicious
would just kidnap 'im.
勝手に連れてってくれりゃ
楽なんだけどな。
えええ…。
アイ？
Hey! What do you think you're saying
in front of this young mother!
おおい！可愛い奥さんが→
お子様の身を案じている時に
何てこと言うんだ！
Uh, like I was saying...
ああ　いや　だから…。
大丈夫です！お子さんは→
Do not worry! I will find him for certain!
俺が必ず見つけ出して
みせますから！
あの…。
U-Um...
はいはいはい…！
はいはい…とおっ！
ぬおお～っ！
とおっ！とおっ！…ハッ！
うん～っ！
オオオ～ッ！
…とおっ！
なるほど　本物の赤ん坊を
背負っていると→
I see now! When I have a real baby on my back, my
reaction time and movements are all on another level!
体のキレ　反射速度　全てが違う。
アア？
今なら　あの男鹿にも…。
As I am now, I can beat him!
《いや　ダメだ…→
Wait, it's no good.
必殺技を完成させない事には
男鹿に勝つことは…》
Before I perfect my new secret
move, beating Oga would be...
アウ…ウ～ア！アイ…。
うん？
アウ…ウ～ア！
ガキは無邪気でいいな。
Kids... Not a care in the world.
ア…ウ～ア！アイ…。
アウ…ウ～ア。
T-That's it!
Eureka!
わかったぞ～！
ウワァ～アア～！アア～！
おおっと！すまねえ。待ってろ→
Sorry 'bout that. Just wait!
すぐ　お前の母ちゃんを
見つけてやるからな。
I'll find your mom soon.
Kota!
（邦枝）光太！
うん？あ？
《な！？男鹿ぁ！？》
Oga?!
あれ？お前たしか…。
Wait, aren't you...
Why does Kanzaki have Kota?
《何で神崎が光太を？
しかも　泣かせてる！？》
And... Kota's crying?
（神崎）うん？お前…。
エッ！？
Aren't you...
（心臓の鼓動）
ああ…。
（邦枝）《今度こそ気づかれた！？》
Is my cover blown this time?
よく見たら…。
After a closer look...
《そ　そりゃそうよね→
Well, it's only normal. We're
both part of the TKKH...
一応は同じ東邦神姫の
一人なんだし！→
ああ～ついにバレちゃうワケ！？》
So, the jig's finally up?
ずいぶん　若い
母ちゃんだな。→
You are quite the young mother.
Perfect timing. I've been
looking for his mom.
ちょうどよかった。
この坊主の母ちゃんを…。
え　いや…。
いかん！子供だけでなく→
No...
You can't! You don't just want
the baby but the mother too?!
奥様までもが狙われている！
はぁ？
Huh?
可愛いお子様を誘拐し
さらには！→
You kidnap the cute kid, and on top of that,
you're trying to lay hands
on his cute, young mother!
その若く美しいお母様まで
手にかけようとは！→
Even for a member of the
TKKH, that's low, Kanzaki!
東邦神姫の一人
神崎も落ちぶれたもんだな！
何だと？
What did you say?
Oga! Do it!
男鹿　やってやりんさい。
やるって？
Do what?
He's a kidnapper. Do what
you always do and blast him.
あいつは誘拐犯だ。いつもの
ように　ぶっとばせばいいんだよ。
いや　いつものようにって…。
It's not what I always do...
ダ～ッ！
ア？アウア～！
ダ～！
アア～ッ！
ダダ～！
ウ～アアア～！
な　何これ？
W-What's this?
It's dangerous, Madam! Don't get close!
きけんです！奥さん！
近寄らない方が。
はあ？
ウ～ウ～ウゥ～…。
そうか…わかった。この俺に
男鹿を倒してほしいんだな？
I see.
I see. You want me to defeat Oga, yes?
ウッ　ウッ。
よ～し。
All right, then.
ここから先は　本気の戦いだ。→
Our real battle starts now.
I can't have you getting hurt.
お前にケガでもさせたら
申し訳ないからな。
ア～　アウア～！
心配すんな。
Don't worry about me.
今までの俺とは違う。
I'm a different man than I once was.
行くぞぉ～！
Here I go!
おい！ちょっと待てって！
Hey! Wait up!
《あのガキが　俺にくれた
必殺技のヒント！》
The hint that kid gave
me for my special move...
((アウ…ウ～ア))
Oga!
男鹿ぁ～！
な！？
あの技は！？
That technique...!
Double Heel Smash!
ダブル踵落とし～！
うわっ！
《決まった！》
I've got it!
あ？
よ…よう。
Yo.
Yo...
あ？
だから　何？
So... What?
ダブ　アイアイ…。
（カラスの鳴き声）
（邦枝）そうなんだ。迷子になった→
I see.
You kept Kota company when he got lost.
光太の相手してくれてたんだね。
（神崎）ああ。
Yeah.
へえ～。
エ　エヘヘヘ…　俺　てっきり→
I figured you were the
weirdo my sister mentioned.
妹を襲った変質者と思って。
勘違いしてごめんなさい。
I'm sorry for the mistake.
It's fine. By the way...
いや…ところで　お前　どっかで
見たことがあるような…。
Have I seen you somewhere before?
え　えっと　きっと人違いだよ！→
H-Huh? Just your imagination!
Definitely!
よくわからないけど
きっとそう！
I'm not sure, but that's definitely it!
ま　いいか。
Fine, whatever.
（光太）アア～！
あ？
ア…ウ～ウ！ウ～ア～…。
それより　男鹿。
あ？
Anyway... Oga!
今日のところは
この子に免じて許してやる。
At this kid's request,
I'll let you off today.
いや　許すも何も…。
Uh, let me off from what exactly?
But the next time we meet will be your last.
だが　次に会った時こそ
お前の最期だ！
Remember that well!
それだけは覚えておけ！
ア～！ウウ～！アア～ウ～。
またな　坊主。
Don't cry, kid.
ああ　そういや
さっきのダブル何とかだっけ？
Oh, yeah... That "Double" something or other.
あ？
あれ　けっこうビックリしたわ。
That was pretty surprising.
フン…。
But seriously... What?
だから　何なの　これ？
（城山）神崎さん！
Kanzaki-san!
やりましたね　ダブル踵落とし！
You did the double heel smash!
For Oga-chan to say it surprised
him, that's really something!
あの男鹿ちゃんが
ビビったって言うんだから→
大したもんだと思うよ～。
（神崎）フン！
待って下さい　神崎さん！
Wait, Kanzaki-san!
We brought you yogurti since
you're likely tired out.
（夏目）
つかれてると思って
ヨーグルッチも買ってきたんだからさ。
You guys...
お前ら…。
フッ…仕方ねえな。
付いて来い！帰るぞ！
Fine, then... Follow me! We're going home!
はっ　はい！
そう来なくちゃね。
R-Right!
That's how it's gotta be!
神崎さ～ん！
フッ…。
Kanzaki-san!
（３人）アハハハ…！
He's finally showed up!
Who has?
Tojo, man! Tojo!
Tojo, of the TKKH! The
strongest man in Ishiyama!
Ooh! Baby Beel's also feelin' it!
On the next Beelzebub: The Delinquents
have Changed into Swimsuits!
I see! Tojo was working at a beach house.
Let's go, Furuichi!
Wait a sec... Did you say, the beach?
Which means... Hilda-san in a swimsuit!